  
  QuizApp.Data.config = {"name": ""};
//SA 
QuizApp.Data.quiz = [
							{"question": "With jQuery, look at the following selector: $(div.intro). What does it select?",
							"questionId": "1",
							"correctAnswer" : "All div elements with class=intro",
							options:[{"option": "The first div element with id=intro"},
									{"option": "The first div element with class=intro"},
									{"option": "All div elements with class=intro"},
									{"option": "All div elements with id=intro"}
									]						 
							},
							
							{"question": "Which jQuery method is used to hide selected elements?",
							"questionId": "2",
							"correctAnswer" : "hide()",
							options:[{"option": "hide()"},
									{"option": "hidden()"},
									{"option": "visible(false)"},
									{"option": "display(none)"}
									]						 
							},
							
							{"question": "Which jQuery method should be used to deal with name conflicts?",
							"questionId": "3",
							"correctAnswer" : "noConflict()",
							options:[{"option": "noConflict()"},
									{"option": "nameConflict()"},
									{"option": "noNameConflict()"},
									{"option": "conflict()"}
									]						 
							},
							{"question": "What is the each function used for?",
							"questionId": "4",
							"correctAnswer" : "The Each function allows you to loop through different elements with a class or ID.",
							options:[{"option": "The Each function allows you to loop though every element in a parent element."},
									{"option": "The Each function allows you to put the word 'Each' into each element."},
									{"option": "The Each function allows you to loop through different elements with a class or ID."},
									{"option": "None of the above."}
									]						 
							},

							{"question": "When do you use the $(this) code?",
							"questionId": "5",
							"correctAnswer" : "When an HTML element will reference its own action.",
							options:[{"option": "When an HTML element will reference its own action."},
									{"option": "When an HTML element will reference its parent element's action."},
									{"option": "When an HTML element will reference the entire document."},
									{"option": "None of the above."}
									]						 
							},

							{"question": "var x = 15, y = 10;console.log(x++-++y);",
							"questionId": "6",
							"correctAnswer" : "4",
							options:[{"option": "5"},
									{"option": "20"},
									{"option": "4"},
									{"option": "30"}
									]						 
							},

							{"question": "console.log(typeof typeof(undefined));",
							"questionId": "7",
							"correctAnswer" : "String",
							options:[{"option": "Object"},
									{"option": "String"},
									{"option": "undefined"},
									{"option": "null"}
									]						 
							},

							{"question": "What does the $.get() jQuery function do?",
							"questionId": "8",
							"correctAnswer" : "It fires a GET AJAX request.",
							options:[{"option": "It fires a GET AJAX request."},
									{"option": "It returns the DOM elements that are contained in the jQuery object."},
									{"option": "None of the above."}
									]						 
							},
							
							
							
							{"question": "Which jQuery method is used to perform an asynchronous HTTP request?",
							"questionId": "9",
							"correctAnswer" : "jQuery.ajax()",
							options:[{"option": "jQuery.ajaxSetup()"},
									{"option": "jQuery.ajaxAsync()"},
									{"option": "jQuery.ajax()"}
									]						 
							},
							
							{"question": "What is the correct jQuery code for making all div elements 100 pixels high?",
							"questionId": "10",
							"correctAnswer" : "$('div').height(100)",
							options:[{"option": "$('div').yPos(100)"},
									{"option": "$('div').height(100)"},
									{"option": "$('div').height='100'"},
									{"option": "conflict()"}
									]						 
							},

							{
							"scorePerQuestion" : "10",
							"correctAnswerCount" : "0",
							"wrongAnswerCount" : "0",		 
							"userScore" : "0",
							"questionCount":"0"							
							},
						];					

//ES
